18313 SW 143rd Place Miami, FL 33177

DOB: 11/23/1999

Phone Number: (305) 968 – 1487 Email: Glissette1999@gmail.com

LISSETTE GARCIA

OBJECTIVE

Motivated college student majoring in pre-veterinary medicine with 2 years of retail and customer service experience. I wish to build my experience and bring forth leadership and create a positive environment by working hard, communicating with my coworkers, teamwork and by boosting morale.

WORK HISTORY

STAFF EMPLOYEE, GIRL SCOUTS OF TROPICAL SOUTH FLORIDA, MIAMI, FL

June 2017 - September 2017

- Filing, taking inventory, and Merchandising any Girl Scouts Products
- Organizing field trips and events
- Recruitment of new girl scouts
- Taking care of and following to-do list for the day with girl scouts

SALES ASSOCIATE, PET SUPERMARKET, MIAMI, FL

August 2018 – July 2019

- Greet each customer and ensure great customer service
- Ensure proper care for animals (rodents, bunnies, reptiles, fish, etc.)
- M7tttttttttttttttttttt
- Merchandise new products
- Ability to work fast in a rapidly changing environment (sales, stocking, customer service, etc.)
- Take charge of register and handle cash

SALES PHOTOGRAPHER, ZOO MIAMI, MIAMI, FL

January 2020 - June 2020

- Greet customers and ensure great customer service
- Edit/Stuff photos into book album
- Sell photo books to families on their way out
- Take charge of register and handle cash

WELLNESS COORDINATOR (FDA), MASSAGE ENVY, COUNTRY WALK

June 2020 - Current

- Greet and ensure great customer service
- Book appointments correctly documenting accurate information
- Guide new clients through their session and ensure they will come back
- Call clients for any updated information needed/run-throughs
- Answer phone calls throughout the day and help clientele with any topic
- Walkthroughs of clinic making sure everything is neat and organized
- Prepare for next day (make pouches for therapists, secure deposits, clean front)

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

Paws 4 You Rescue Organization, Miami

January 2017 - February 2019

- Take care/responsibility of animals (taking them on walks, playing with them, bathing them if need be)
- Helping interested customers learn about how to adopt, learn about the company, foster programs, and how to help and volunteer.
- Ensuring great customer service to try and find our animals a forever home.

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, ROBERT MORGAN EDUCATIONAL CENTER (2018)

Academy of Hospitality & Tourism

ASSOCIATES OF ARTS DEGREE, MIAMI DADE COLLEGE (2019 – PRESENT)

Majoring in Pre Veterinary Science

SKILLS

- Ability to create strong customer relationships
- Able to communicate in English and Spanish
- Quickly adaptable to any work environment
- Experience working in a fast-paced environment
- Fast thinking and problem-solving skills
- Certified in PowerPoint, Word, Photoshop, and illustrator

Page | 2 Lissette Garcia